мукута ткасник

MOBILE: +351914025704

E-mail: nick.tkachuk@gmail.com

LINKED-IN: NICK TKACHUK

TL; DR

Over 14 years in QA. Performed manual, and automated, performance testing for a wide variety of products. Experienced in cloud-based web ecosystems and mobile application testing. Preferably agile. Interested in security testing.



Programming Languages: Python, Javascript, Ruby
Operating Systems: Windows, *nix, Mac, Android, iOS
<pre>Development\Testing Tools: Testomat.io, Cypress, VS Code, Heroku, PyCharm, RubyMine, Jenkins, BurpSuite, Jmeter, Postman, Kibana, etc.</pre>

Experience:

Senior QA engineer at Faster Than Light

Nov 2021 - Dec 2023

API testing

Web-testing

Mobile testing (iOS\Android)

Cypress automation

Test strategy development

Javascript

GitHub Actions

Senior QA engineer at Zoolatech

Feb 2020 - Oct 2021

API testing

Mobile testing (iOS)

Ruby\Rails

Senior QA engineer in ORM\Ciklum

May 2019 - Feb 2020

☐ Various test-types execution
☐ Mobile testing (iOS and Android)
☐ API testing

☐ FrontEnd Web testing
☐ Test documentation creation and maintenance
☐ Development and Delivery lifecycle management
☐ Performance testing (Jmeter\Blazemeter)
UI testing, Functional testing, Jira, TestRail, Jenkins, Postman, Javascript, WdIO
Senior QA engineer in Keypr\Intelity
January 2014 - December 2018
☐ Various test-types execution
☐ Mobile testing (iOS and Android)
□ API testing
☐ FrontEnd Web testing
☐ Test documentation creation and maintenance
□ Development and Delivery lifecycle management
☐ Functional map and documentation creation and maintenance
Logs analysis, UI testing, Functional testing, Jira, TestRail, Jenkins, Android, iOS, API testing
Automation Engineer/ Software test engineer at Persha Studia (Wargaming) October 2013 - November 2014
☐ Various test-types execution
☐ Web Portal automation test creation
☐ Scrum process participation
☐ Localization testing
☐ Providing full cycle of bug management (analyzing and verifying) Selenium-based automation framework (Webium), python, Jira, Confluence, TestRail, Teamcity
Software test engineer at Ciklum
April 2011 - October 2012
☐ Android apps testing
☐ Test Plan creation
lacksquare Test case creation and execution
lacksquare Test Automation using the "Monkey Runner" framework
MonkeyRunner, Jira, Java.
Software test engineer/ Team leader at Quest Software
April 2010 - January 2011
☐ Test Plan creation
Performing requirement/functional specifications analysis; requirements decomposition
☐ Test environment setup
lacksquare Execution tests of various types
☐ Interviewing new candidates
☐ Junior QA Training Plan creation
☐ Mentoring
VMWare ESX, Jira, TestRail, InstallAnywhere, Vizioncore VA, Jmeter

Automation test engineer at GlobalLogic
November 2009 - April 2010
☐ Finding and submitting bugs
☐ Writing automated test scripts for Selenium Remote Control using Ruby with Cucumber extension
☐ Participate in planning iterations structure
☐ Make estimations for testing/test writing works
☐ New build deployment
☐ Web Application testing
Selenium Remote Control, Selenium IDE, Ruby, Cucumber, Jira, Bamboo, TeamCity,
PostgreSQL Software Test Engineer, Performance test engineer at GlobalLogic
April 2008 - May 2009
☐ Product functional map creation
lacksquare Performance test development and result analysis
☐ Direct customer communication
□ Summary reporting
Jmeter, Jira, Java
Software Quality Engineer at GlobalLogic
April 2006 - April 2008
Performing requirement/functional specifications analysis; requirements decomposition
☐ Performance test development
☐ Developing and executing test cases
☐ Executing tests of various types; full-scale functional tests ☐
Providing full cycle of bug management (analyzing and verifying) \Box
Regression testing: retesting closed defects, affected functionality
LoadRunner, Bugzilla, Jira, Oracle SQL, .NET, Java, MS SQL 2008, VBS, OS X, FreeBSD
System Administrator at Architectural Bureau "U.Lositsky"
May 2002 - April 2006
☐ Setup and maintenance of a small office company
□ Network configuration and maintenance
FreeBSD, Home / Small Office IT Support service
Education:
☐ "IT Step" Academy -Specialist, Network and System Administration 2003 - 2006
☐ National Taras Shevchenko University - Bachelor of Education
Spoken Languages:
English - fluent, Ukrainian/Russian - native, Portuguese - basic